? Come on ?
? Ha, sicker than your average ?
? Poppa twist cabbage off instinct ?
? Don't think shit stink, pink gators ?
? My Detroit players ?
? Timbs for my hooligans in Brooklyn, that's right ?
? Dead right, if the head right ?
? Biggie there e'ry night ?
? Poppa been smooth since days of Underoos...
嘿 雷吉 碣I的了
Hey, yo, Reggie! Re-up.
? Biggie, Biggie, Biggie, can't you see? ?
? Sometimes your words just hypnotize me ?
? And I just love your flashy ways ?
的
Shit.
? Guess that's why they broke and you're so paid ?
? Biggie, Biggie, Biggie, can't you see ?
你不是病得太重 o法了
I thought you were too sick to practice.
不再去了 教
Done with all that, Coach.
你很久都]吃D像拥娘了吧
When's the last time you had a decent meal?
走吧
Come on.
是g迎你砦壹页燥的
Mary's always happy to have you at the table.
你f什么都不改我的想法
Nothing you say is gonna change my mind.
死的 雷吉
Damn it, Reggie.
你是我^的最有才A的超英雄
You're the most talented superhero I've ever seen.
而你s浪M自己的才A 秃拓毒
Yet you're... you're throwing it all away slinging yayo for gangbangers?
你不了解我 教 你什么都不知道
You don't know me, Coach. You don't know nothin'.
我知道你有良知
I know you've got heart.
我知道你不想@悠活
I know you want more than this.
你是有x竦 孩子
You've got a choice, son.
要么克服困y 好好活下去
Either outrun this life,
要么害自己早早M入墓
or you can run yourself into an early grave.
求你了 我是你的布林克教啊
Now, please. It's me, Coach Brink.
跟我回去吧
Come back with me.
回到郊^去
To the suburbs.
我想要什么并不重要
Yeah, what I want doesn't matter.
我永h都o法[街^ξ业挠绊
I'll never be free of these streets.
- 停 天哪  - 停了
Cut! Holy fuck.
天哪 @一段拍得太好了
Holy fuck, we're not gonna beat that.
太他完美了 再硪淮
That was fucking perfect. We're going again.
M雷斯特里普太牛逼了  噙著I水哦
Ferrell fucking Streep. There are tears.
真正的I水
Literal tears.
用周末在康普D青年中心 w生活真是明智啊
Who's happy they spent two weekends at the Compton Youth Center now, huh?
我的表演人想起《弱c》
I'm not giving off too much of a Blind Side vibe, am I?
那也不是氖掳 你... 等等 什么味
As if that's a bad thing? Are you-- Wait, what is that smell?
- 都我f 有股什么味  - 什么
- Will everyone stop? - What is that smell?!
是...
Is it...
- 是你  - 我午餐吃的豆丸子三明治
- Is that you? - I had falafel for lunch.
怎么了
What?
我到了W斯卡提名的味道
I smell an Oscar nomination.
得了吧 伙
Shut up, man.
- 我是f真的 - e貘f嘴
No, I won't. Don't jinx it.
貘f嘴φ娼]用 看著我
You can't jinx gold. Look at me.
s快在架子上v出小金人的位置吧 大明星 到了
You better make some shelf space, De Niro. Do you hear me?
好啦 快去浒
All right, let's get you back to one, huh?
- 我去看回放 - 然
- I'm gonna watch playbacks, okay? - Absolutely.
o他一副耳C xx
Yeah, let's get him some cans, please? Thank you.
快速解Q一件事 我在上f一下
One more quick thing. Let's sidebar here a little bit.
感X你很y[新手的青
It feels like you're having a little bit of trouble getting out of the starters' block.
也S是鼍暗}吧
Maybe it's the scene.
@鼍昂玫貌坏昧 看著我
Baby, this scene sings. All right, look at me.
你@角色的l展曲中 @r候是最低c
In the arc of your character, this is your low point, right?
每人都想放你 你o依o靠 直到教...
Everybody's given up on you, you're all alone, until the coach--
突然F身 把我呢民窟里解救出
Swoops in and saves me from the ghetto?
不 你H上拯救了彼此 @是一N非常平衡的⑹率址
No, no, no, you actually save each other. It's a very balanced narrative.
我聘的所有敏感x者 都同意@一c
All the sensitivity readers that we hired, they all agreed.
我哥是我唯一的教
My brother was the only coach I ever had.
是
Right.
但他是巴斯特比弗餐d的服T 不是什么他的毒
He was a waiter at Buster Beaver, not a fucking crack dealer.
他F在一定槟愀械津傲
And he must be so proud of you right now.
我接著好好拍虬
Let's get this train back on the tracks.
- o我crg - 然可以
- Just give me a minute. - Yeah, sure.
等等 知道嘛 有件小事
Wait, wait, you know what? One more tiny little thing.
你才f“我想要什么并不重要”
You said what I want "doesn't matter."
但H上”旧系呐_~ 是“我想要什么并不重”
But as scripted, it's actually what I want "don't matter," okay?
好 好 不e
All right, good stuff.
好吧 各位 重拍一次
All right, everybody, let's get back to one!
我想今天拍好
I want to make this fucking day!
嘿 我可以
Hey, can we talk?
你不f 你就@一特征
You don't talk. It's like your one thing.
扮演玄色是一有意x的挑
Look, playing Noir has been a meaningful challenge,
但昨天真是太他的xV了
but yesterday was wack as fuck.
我以前]真正⑦^人
I've never actually murdered anyone before.
祖人我⑷
Does Homelander make us kill people, like, a lot?
他我⑷r 我就...照k
And when he does, do we just... do it?
著 e`我的意思 我很高d加入F
Look, don't get me wrong, I am stoked to be here
我已浜米プC遇了
and I am down to ride the wave. I'm just having trouble
我只是π色的C感到困惑 你明白我的意思
with Noir's motivation, you feel me?
他的C是做一X死亡的子
His motivation is being a braindead maniac.
把嘴]上
Just keep your mouth shut
照他的吩咐去做
and do as you're fucking told.
在我血E斑斑的街道上 φ派 勤诘拿人的施暴
Violence in our blood-splattered streets against decent, hardworking Americans.
各位 如果您想自己的孩子 在室外ono]地玩耍
Folks, if you're thinking of letting your children
不需要有人看管地玩耍 可要三思啊
play carefree outside and without supervision, think again.
我是f @禽F 本尼朗和伊恩拉什福德
I mean, these two animals, Benny Long and Ian Rashford,
昨天在法院外野U地⑷名好人打死
savagely beat three good men to death outside the courthouse yesterday.
伙 星光支持者 已露出了他的真面目
The Starlighters have shown their true colors, folks,
在全各地多次所^的和平示威上
rioting at multiple quote-unquote "peaceful demonstrations"
制造}y
across the country.
就我而言 我J樵谖@ゴ蟮 家里 自由并不是理所然的
I, for one, do not take our liberties in this great country for granted.
但@然 星光支持者有不同的想法
But apparently the Starlighters feel differently.
看看 大豆{pH值
Let's see. Soy for pH,
透明|酸用于深颖 精氨酸用于...
hyaluronic acid for deep moisturizing and arginine for circulation.
那些是什么|西
What is all that?
我是一名沃特值
Um, I'm a Voughtality consultant.
倒是]什么治作用
5K away from the red, white and blue Caddy.
- 我J檫@可能有助于... - 你...你在沃特工作
- I thought it might be helpful. - You... You work for Vought?
沃特值 “打理超人的你”
Voughtality. "For a Super You."
你知道沃特⒘宋遗朋友
You know Vought killed my girlfriend, right?
我F在正在c他鸲
I'm literally fighting them right now.
我想我是有迷迭香精油的
I think I have rosemary oil,
它P很有好
it's really good for the joints.
你能...e弄那些了 就...
Can you just-- Can you stop please? Just for--
- 不要弄了 住手 e弄了  - Σ黄
- Please stop. Mom, stop. Just stop. - Okay, I'm sor--
天哪 Σ黄 只是...
Okay, sorry, sorry. Just, um...
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
你看起聿诲e
You look good.
L高了
Got tall.
f得通啊 你上次到我
Yeah, that adds up, since the last time you saw me
- 我他的才六q  - eξ掖蠛按蠼
- I was six fucking years old! - Please don't yell at me.
- 你磉@里有何F干  - t院o我打了
- What are you doing here? - The hospital called.
那是因樗系不上我 而我F在已砹 所以...
Yeah, when they couldn't reach me. And I'm here now, so...
他不需要你 我z都不需要你
He doesn't need you. Neither of us do.
你爸]告V你
Your dad didn't tell you.
死
Shit.
告V我什么
About what?
他o了我授 包括做tQ定的嗬
He gave me power of attorney, including medical decisions.
他署了一份 拒^心肺吞Kg的t指示
And he signed a DNR.
他]有更新z
H-He didn't update his will?
更新了
He did.
你倒是ff他怎么o你授 s不o我
Why the fuck would he give you power of attorney over me?
我知道 我是f ^去的一赡昀
Well, I mean, we've been talking, the last year or two,
我一直有系
now and then.
偶系 我...除此之外 你得要求他o你授嗖判
Besides that, you'd have to ask him.
但是 休伊 e心
But Hughie, don't worry,
- 我很擅L理危C - e...
- I am really good in a crisis. - Don't.
我可以理@件事
And I-I-I can handle this.
我保C
I promise.
你保C
You promise.
休伊 等等
Hughie... Wait.
你把X留在梳y_上了
You leave the money on the dresser?
我不想吵醒你
I didn't want to wake you up.
嘿
Hey.
也S你今天P床休息 不是
Yeah, maybe you should stay in bed today, no?
是的
Yeah...
@已算幸\了
Could've been a lot worse.
我是f 如果你r不在龅脑 情r更糟
I mean, it would've been a lot worse if you weren't there.
xx
Thank you.
工作
Work.
你的Z言治格洛
Your speech therapist Gloria
告V我你都做了哪些努力
has filled me in on the work you've been doing.
M展如何
How's that been going?
要是M展利的 我就不磉@里了
你知道 心理沉默Y
You know, psychological mutism
通常是一人^往 表F出的Y
is often a symptom of trauma in one's past.
你Υ擞泻慰捶
What do you think about that?
我的^去并不塑造我
我完全同意 但有r
I couldn't agree more. But sometimes
你必面ψ约旱倪^去才能[它
you have to confront your past in order to be free of it.
好吧 不如我先娜菀椎氖虑槿胧
Okay. Why don't we start with something simple?
跟我vv你的父母
Tell me about your parents.
天哪 你F在才告V我
Jesus. You're just telling us now?
你去找？漆t生看^ 你...
Have you seen any specialists, have you, um...
- 那么 你有多久可活  - @他的不P你的事
- So how long you got? - It's none of your fucking business.
@是怎么了
What's going on?
不知道槭裁次乙告V你 我有守o天使
I'm not sure why I'm telling you at all.  Let's just say I got an angel on my shoulder.
她Z叨]完
And she's a right bloody nag.
布 我D警告^你那|西有毒
Butcher, I tried to warn you that that shit was poison.
你又不是我F的一T
You ain't one of us.
- 嘿  - 好啦
- Hey! - All right!
我
A word.
- 你走人吧 - 什么
- You're done. - What?
你被解雇了 拿上你的|西L蛋吧
Fired. Grab your shit and get the fuck out.
我δ坦\相待 你就@么感x我
I level with you lot and this is the thanks I get.
真他的 看看\硎裁春蠊
Fuck me. See what being honest gets you?
\ ^去六月里 你一直在ξ撒e
Honest? Motherfucker, you've been lying to us for the last six months.
不f不等于fe
Not telling ain't lying.
著 你需要各N各拥脑助 伙
Look, you need all the help you can get, mate.
不需要你援助 你是 布
Not from you. You're a liability, Butcher.
那我就不^m了
I ain't gonna let this stand, then.
英雄克星是我的
The Boys is mine.
你@是一垂死之人最后一次吹牛
Says a dying man with one last bluff.
F在拿上你的|西L蛋吧
Now grab your shit and get the fuck out.
不然我就把你s出去
Or I'll throw you out.
- 就... - 我不想 他得走人
- Just... - I don't want to hear it. He's out.
不M的 你可以跟他一起走人
You can join him if you don't like it.
英雄克星
第四季第二集
本WEB版外熳帜挥  L吹淼哪瞧云  pZ合并
小孩子跟著 在蒙大拿州的牧鲩L大
Small-town kid grows up on a Montana ranch with his mom.
谋砻嫔峡 他是一普通的 典型的美男孩
On the surface, he's an everyday all-American boy.
但在刃纳钐 他知道自己c不同 很特e
But deep in his heart, he knows he's different, special.
他是自己:“我是l ”
He's always asking himself, "Who am I?"
有一天 @}得到了解答
Then one day that question is answered
因樽人奶於降
when Homelander flies down from the sky
- 眼里含著I水... - ]有I水
- and says with tears in his eyes-- - No tears.
他自豪地f “鹤 是r候你站在我身了”
and says, proudly, "Son, it's time for you to take your place by my side."
R恩X得@事令人@ 但s是不可避免的
And for Ryan it feels surprising, yet inevitable.
他一直都知道自己注定出人^地
He always knew he was destined for greatness.
因樗出身于ゴ
Because he came from greatness.
鹤 X得y以置信吧
Oh, buddy, can you believe that?
祖男孩
你X得怎么
W-What do you think?
很酷
It's cool,
我感X
I guess.
你感X
You guess?
- 我X得棒O了 - 哦 太棒了
- I think it looks amazing. - Oh, so amazing.
- 非常有N路 - 非常有N路
- Really marketable. - So marketable.
@意太假了
The whole pitch blows.
它...才不假呢
It... does not blow.
比米高梅片瞿舷＠锔那出假
It blows, harder than Nancy Reagan on the MGM backlot.
Σ黄 你磉@里做什么
I'm sorry, why are you here?
火之后 沃特解雇了 大部分超英雄的伙伴
Vought got rid of most of the sidekicks after Gunpowder.
不惜付超出他盈利能力的解雇金
The settlements exceeded profitability.
是的 但我J槿R恩不 向人力Y源部T投V我
Yeah, but I don't think Ryan is gonna file an HR complaint against me.
什么
A what?
R恩是第一天生的超英雄 λM行推Vr需要反映出@一c
Ryan is the first natural-born superhero. And his brand needs to reflect that.
他不是Q生于沃特室的怪胎
He's not one of Vought's lab rat freaks.
他是被命\或上帝x中
He was chosen-- by fate, God, whatever--
成檎救世界的人
to be the one who saves the world.
是的
Yes.
但我不要忘 他的特e碓从诤翁 不是
But let's not forget why he is special. Shall we?
他是我的鹤
He's my son.
然是神x之子
Chosen by God, sure,
但是...是我造出淼
but, uh... made by me.
“天x之人”的⑹ 只孤英雄才有效
The chosen one narrative only works if he stands alone.
哈利波特 尼W R克天行者
Harry Potter. Neo. Luke Skywalker.
好R]人喜 白人男孩做孤救世主
Hollywood's trained people to fall in love with white boy lone saviors.
所以 美想要凵先R恩的
So, America will want to fall in love with Ryan.
沃特《H犯罪》
@是什么
What is this?
@是犯罪 你要首次救援了 恭喜你 鹤
Uh, it's a crime itinerary. Your first save. Congratulations, son.
我]在拍zrg表上
I'm not on the call sheet.
你想樽约旱鹤咏立一王
You wanted a kingdom for your son.
我正在湍F@目
I'm helping you get it.
很好 正如我的那
Excellent. Just as we discussed.
你看著k吧
Feel free to move forward.
xx
Thanks.
你不介意照合影吧
Ah, if you don't mind?
我在@里是因樽人要我在@里
I'm here because Homelander wants me here.
因樗信任我
Because he trusts me.
著 我知道 你是地球上最明的女人
Listen. I know you're the smartest woman on earth--
最明的人
Smartest person.
我o你c建h吧
Let me give you some advice.
我女孩互相支持嘛
You know, girls supporting girls.
你不能那痈祖人f
You cannot talk to Homelander like that.
我在v真
I'm telling him the truth.
你太怕他了 得B^l都拔光了
You're so afraid of him, you've plucked yourself bald.
如果我是你 我自己得有用
If I were you, I'd make myself useful.
_始分泌乳汁 好他吮吸你的乳^吧
You know, get some lactation going, let him suck on those titties.
不然就落得 德琳斯蒂威那拥南
Before you end up like Madelyn Stillwell.
艾 你好
Oh, Ashley, hey, what's up?
我正想你@位女老板呢
Just the girl boss I wanted to see.
我一直在四找你呢
I've been looking everywhere for you.
我fR恩要M行第一次为救援
Hey, so I heard that Ryan's doing his first solo save.
我想和你 我有想法
I want to talk to you about something. I have this idea.
那么 要是...
Okay, so, what if...
我f完
and just hear me out on this,
要是他救援之前我到隽嗽趺
what if I was there?
就@事 就是@想法
That's it. That's the pitch.
你想加入 m合全家老少^看的拯救行
Hmm. You want to join a family-friendly PG save?
e忘了 你在善待游锝M的 F交^察名紊
While PETA still has you on their bestiality watchlist?
我向上帝l誓
I swear to God.
自以槁明的蠢人 真他的我抓狂
Stupid people who think they're smart make me want to eat my own shit.
你槭裁丛试S她@痈你f
Why do you let her talk to you like that?
她只是婊子
She's just a bitch.
也S她泶笠了
It's probably that time of the month.
M月的r候就 不是
It's like a full moon thing, isn't it?
你是一基因越的人
You're a genetically superior being,
在M化上 她相于水豚
and she's the evolutionary equivalent of a capybara.
- 水什么  - 水豚 一N南美洲的巨型X游
- Cappuccino...? - It's a giant rodent from South America.
你比她更秀 表F得秀c
You're better than her. Act like it.
你⑴c救援
And you should be at the save.
@是好主意
It's a good idea.
xx
Thank you.
1c16分 托德和其他 祖人支持者M入了沃特星球大B
1:16, Todd and the other Hometeamers are seen going into Planet Vought.
直到2c09分才再次F身
And not seen again until... 2:09,
r 他的尸w 神奇地出F在了集上
when their dead bodies magically appear at the rally.
你X得他是如何 神不知鬼不X地出F的
Now, how do you think they got there without anybody seeing?
火^ 肯定是火^
A-Train. It had to be A-Train.
保C 就像你ξ野直ＷC不x不
You promise? Like you promised Dad for better or worse?
我你o聊了 休伊
We boring you, Hughie?
抱歉 我在...
Sorry. Sorry. I'm, um...
我著呢
I'm here.
但@些祖人支持者死于g器外
But the Hometeamers died of blunt force trauma.
]有任何P于超能力致死的信息
Nothing said anything about super strength.
因樗越碓缴瞄L掩w自己了
Because they're getting a lot better at covering their ass,
大概是因樗吧
probably because of her.
智者姐妹 32q 碜悦苄根州底特律
Sister Sage. 32 years old, from Detroit, Michigan.
早先他把她s出英雄少年r 她就c沃特嘟^了P系
She cut ties with Vought a while back, when they kicked her off of Teenage Kix.
- 她有什么超能力  - 地球上最明的人
- What are her powers? - Smartest person on the planet.
我已O了智者的手C
I've already tapped Sage's cell phones.
她在位于哈里斯堡的
She made a reservation at the Vought Garden
沃特花@套房庭院快捷酒店 定了房g
Suites & Courtyard Express in Harrisburg tonight.
l想去跑一趟
Who's down for a little road trip?
知道嘛 我要留在@里
You know what? I'm gonna stay here.
如果火^陷害了那星光支持者 我就要跟他拼命
If A-Train framed those two Starlighters, I'm gonna take a run at him.
我...我跟你一起
I-I'm gonna go with you.
- 我必o理我爸 - 理解
- I got to stay close to my dad. - Understood.
好吧 你和我一起去
All right. You two are with me.
看 她做了一可鄣男... o和G丸
Aw, look, she made a cute little... penis and balls.
快c 把X拿
Hurry up, get the money.
- 完蛋了 你墨西哥死鬼 - 退后
- Lights out, you fucking muff taco. - Get back!
玄色
Noir.
- 往后退  - 好吧 冷oc 伙
- Back off. - Hey, whoa, be cool, man.
玄色 我怎么k
Noir, what are we supposed to do?
- 放_她 - e趼 孩子
- Let her go. - Out of my way, kid.
- ]事的 - 你保C
- It's gonna be okay. - Do you promise?
我保C
I promise.
你是l
Who are you?
我叫R恩 我不喜g喊
My name is Ryan. And I don't like bullies.
很好 不e
It's good. Pretty good.
越碓胶昧 拍得好 伙
It's getting better. Solid work, guys.
玄色 你的出鲇悬c^火 用走的就好
Noir, your entrance, you're doing too much. Just walk in.
但玄色走著出
Okay, but would Noir just enter stage right like that?
我感X他奶於降才
I feel like it's more in character if I come in through the skylight.
- 你他的不f - Σ黄
- You don't fucking talk. - Sorry.
在f
Still talking.
我F在就先@幼呶 好
Let's just stick to the blocking for now, okay?
深海 不要f“墨西哥死鬼”
Deep, drop the "fucking muff taco,"
- 男女老少都要看的 - 好的
- this is for families. - Okay.
R恩 拍r 你要真把我出去
Ryan, on the day, you're gonna throw me for real.
- 我能受得住 - 好
- I can take it. - Yeah.
休息五分 再硪槐
Let's take five and we'll run it back.
好的
- Great. - Okay.
xx你 科伊
Thank you, Koy.
- 爸爸  - 什么事
- Dad? - Yeah.
我看起...很蠢
Did I look dumb?
你真的...你必全力以赴 知道
You really... You got to put your back into it.
得...真的人信服
You know, like... You really got to sell it.
明白
You understand?
救援都是@拥
Are all saves like this?
有特技演T 排之的
Like, with stunt people and rehearsals and stuff?
不 然 有些救援是真的 我救^很多人
No, no, of course some of them are real. I-I've saved a lot of people.
@只是榱椭你 m淼恼救援 好
This is just to help you get your sea legs, all right?
- 好的 - 好
- Okay. - Yeah.
R恩 你想 把我出去的那
Hey, Ryan. You want to rehearse the throw a few times?
- 好主意 好 非常棒 - 好 ]}
- Great idea. Yes! - Yeah. Sure.
好
Yes. Excellent.
我想清楚
Hey, so, um, just to be clear,
拍那天我不真的⑷
we're not actually killing people on the day, am I right?
]上你的臭嘴
Just shut the fuck up.
步E要精_
Just be real precise with your steps,
- ~步 抓住  行  - 行
you understand?
你不能那痈我f
You can't talk to me that way.
我什么也]f
I didn't say anything.
我f的是之前
I mean from before.
~步 然后...α
我是...我是人M化的峰
Because I am the... I'm the peak of human evolution.
而你只是...你只是一只“水吞”
And you're just, you're just a capabarnia.
一N南美洲的X游
It's a rodent from South America.
F在你他的是地哺乳游锪
So you're fucking land mammals now?
我是七大洋之主
I am the lord of the seven seas.
你再那么跟我f
You talk to me like that again
我就他的把你淹死在R桶里 你愚蠢的母狗
and I will drown you in your fucking toilet, you stupid bitch.
我拉完屎的R桶
After I've used it.
- 想要我那么δ  - 不想
- Is that what you want? - No.
- 叫先生  - 不想 先生
-"Sir"! - No, sir.
@硬
That's right.
α
- 放_她 - e趼 孩子
- Let her go. - Out of my way, kid.
那孩子的真上R
That kid's face is made for the big screen.
皮w嫩滑 容光òl
A complexion like butter. He's practically glowing.
感x上帝
Well, thank God.
《超七人新o元》中 消除y的工作
Air-brushing the wrinkles out of The Dawn of the Seven
X特效超出A算九百f美元
put VFX nine mil over the budget.
跟《欲望都市2》差不多了
We were neck fold to neck fold with Sex and the City 2.
沃特花@套房庭院快捷酒店
混蛋
Motherfucker.
要蒸汽P里的炒蛋
Fancy some steam tray eggs?
- 你他的是怎么找到我的  - 得了吧 伙
- How the fuck did you find us? - Come off it, mate.
你的密a是“珍妮2012”
Your password's Janine2012.
布 放下P子 e插手我的行
I want you to put that shit down and get the fuck out of my operation.
你不再是我的上司了 我可真幸\啊
Well, it's lucky for me that you ain't my boss no more.
作橐P心此事的普通公民
And as a private and concerned citizen,
我可以θ魏 D阻止我了解真相的混蛋
I'm allowed to say fuck you to any deep state cunts
f“操你”
that try and keep me from the truth.
g迎淼胶镒羽^
Welcome to the monkey house.
真相大
]有\或巧合
安息吧 美
《小S人大眼萌》是奴化教育
安息
_科他U勃Z取大量美人的`魂
鞭炮你看真相
词值拿婵
秘密揭  士兵男孩被中央情缶址
士兵男孩和自由女是秘密情人
白人嗔壅的你
L暴活著
星光正在\⑽
都是些人模狗拥募{粹混蛋
Bunch of tinfoil-hat-wearing Nazi motherfuckers.
槭裁词澜缟献盥明的人 出F在@N地方
Why is the world's smartest person in a place such as this?
和自由斗士 我要求立即放所有和
找到她了
Oi. There's our girl.
喜美子哪去了
Where's Kimiko?
? You can be what you wanna be ?
? In the land of the free ?
? Love America, love America ?
鞭炮你看真相
? If you want it to get better ?
? Open up your loving arms ?
星光c好R]偻癖\集F
? Try to keep them safe from harm ?
? You can say what you want to say ?
? Because freedom is the only way...
斯普林特 ^
Splinter. Splinter, come here.
我的y面反光
Am I too shiny?
你很漂亮 你...完美
You're good. You look perfect.
? Love America...
最好快c 地平者四c半要用@龅
Best get a move on. The Flat-Earthers get the space at 4:30.
好的
Yes. Okay.
嘿 各位
H-Hey, everybody.
下一位演v者 不H是位真正的粝爰
Um, so, our next speaker is not only a true visionary,
也是我的好朋友
she's also my close friend.
和我一起g迎作家 影制作人
So please join me in welcoming author, filmmaker,
政治活蛹 u家
political activist, commentator
以及油管W上 另超人的I人物
and a leading voice of the alt-Supe movement on YouTube,
鞭炮
Firecracker!
你好 真相的探ふ
Well, howdy there, Truth Seekers.
嘿
Hey!
Hey there!
xx
Aw, well, thank you, thank you.
- Io你 好 - 跟鞭炮看真相
Tell us some truth, Firecracker! Okay.
我不粉@一c
I ain't gonna sugarcoat this.
我陷入了家危C
We got ourselves a national crisis.
祖人自己f:“星光u孩子”
Homelander himself said Starlight traffics kids
她的星光支持者昨天\⒘
and her Starlighters just murdered three of our brothers
我三兄弟硌谏w@件事
yesterday to cover it up.
他正在⒑ξ 醒戆
They're killing us. Wake up.
在接下淼小r里 我C明星光
Over the next two hours, I will prove that Starlighter works with Oprah
cW普拉和姆h克斯合作 建立了邪旱乃拓上T服
and Tom Hanks to set up a Satanic home delivery service.
c峁肪得到一男孩 c塔可就得到一女孩
An order of a hot dog gets you a boy. A taco, a girl.
c套餐就得到一 被他迫做性手g的孩子
A combo gets you a child they forced to have trans surgery.
cK打水可以得到一I上腺素
And a soda gets you a shot of adrenochrome.
我都知道...
We all know
居然有人相信@N鬼
People actually believe this shit?
人什么都相信
People will believe anything.
甚至像登月@涌尚Φ氖虑橐相信
Even something as ludicrous as the moon landing.
...但因橛赂业母婷苷
that's because the brave whistleblower who was gonna blow
要把阿甘的偻真相揭_的告密者
Forrest Gump's pedo ring wide open
]l就蛏系袅讼氯
fell off a bridge before he got the chance.
法m奇 看看他要干什么
Frenchie. See what he's up to.
是巧合
Coincidence?
不要跟他交手
But do not engage.
好
Right.
如果把...
Ah, ah, ah.
你不能x_我的
You're ain't leaving my sight.
...姆h克斯影名字的 所有字母盗考釉谝黄
...of all of the Tom Hanks movies,
就得出311 @是...
you get 311, which is...
“和色情”的警方代a W可不_人
the police code for child porn. It's just math!
20分后播放 《L暴支持者FY一心》
Stormchasers United is starting in 20 minutes in conference room B.
收到1l信息 科林 多媒w短信服D像
午餐去悲沙拉吃
嘿 住手 e o我
Hey, stop, no. Give it back.
是@吧
e再娘毫
Stop being a pussy.
去享受科林的o 或者屁股
Go get some of Colin's penis... or ass...
要不都
Or maybe both?
但是去享受吧
But go get it!
你醉了
Are you drunk?
我才喝了一罐啤酒
I just had a beer.
四罐啤酒
Four beers.
你怎么了
What is wrong with you?
六罐啤酒
Six beers.
你因槲叶科林q豫不Q
You're holding back with Colin because of me!
什么 不 @...@c你oP
What? No, it's... It's nothing to do with you.
好吧 我干了一人
Well I fucked someone.
真的
Really?
吉特咖啡^的咖啡
The barista at Jitter Bean.
他把他的o插M了我的道
He stuck his penis right in my vagina.
好吧
Okay.
你把你的o插入某地方
You should stick your penis somewhere!
真心感x
Mon coeur, truly, merci.
但@c你oP 我l誓
But it's not about you, I swear.
v克斯斯模仿秀大已改...
The Alex Jones look-alike contest is in...
我F在可以接著工作了
Can we go back to work now?
八罐啤酒
Eight beers.
收到1l信息 深海{洋房g 晚上九c
@是要干什么
What's that about?
好爽
不是你想的那
This isn't what it looks like.
]P系
It's okay.
南河I公@
你在沃特塔的人_你
Maybe your source at the Tower is fucking with you?
不 如果她f火^每周日 下午三c都磉@里 他就一定
No, no, no, if she says A-Train shows up here every Sunday at 3:00 p.m., he will.
你保C 你的保C和你一雍or值
Yeah, you promise? Your promise is as worthless as you are.
什么
What?
Σ黄 我只是...
Sorry. Sorry, I was just, uh...
在j我怎么跟我f
workshopping what I should've said to my mom.
你真的不必^ 你可以去t院 你去
You really don't have to be here, okay? You can go to the hospital, you should.
不 那里]什么需要我做的 只我...
No. No. No, nothing to do there except, uh...
重匚彝年的
relive my childhood trauma.
三名祖人的支持者被\⒑ 局莞叨染o
Tensions are high after the murder of the Homelander Three
Q 作案者是擅星光的追S者
allegedly at the hands of two Starlight followers.
膳芍g的小_突已...
Skirmishes between the two groups have--
好了 e那些屁了 基拉醒砹
All right, enough of that shit. Uh, has Kiara woken up yet?
]有 另外 我收到了好多信息
No, and I have about a thousand messages
我星光支持者怎么k
asking me what the Starlighters should do.
f吧
Spit it out.
人敬仰你
People look up to you.
不 他敬仰的是星光 他敬仰的是那套鹨
No, they look up to Starlight. They look up to the suit.
可穿著那套鹨碌娜耸悄
You're the one who wore it.
我懂你槭裁捶那身份
I get why you ditched it, I do.
只是...我也能看到其中的r值
It's just, I can also see the value in it.
超英雄的r值
In superheroes?
你F在在捍l超英雄 不吧
You're defending superheroes right now? Really?
M管@起砗芩 但人需要一象征
As cheesy as it sounds, people need a symbol.
某他FY起 而追S的人 o他一cc希望的人
You know, someone they can rally behind, a little fucking hope.
你可以成槟人
That can be you.
我不想I任何人
I don't want to lead anybody. I don't.
我不想 我也不能做回星光
And I cannot go back to her.
ξ碚f 她只是...
To me... she's just,
她是S多氖碌南笳 我...我k不到
she's a symbol of so much bad shit, and I-I can't.
我k不到 我不那么做 就是...就...
I can't. I won't. It's just, it's...
我是f...
Yeah, I mean...
天哪 他砹
Oh, God. He's here, he's here.
我在沃特塔 Π
So I'm at the Tower, right?
我接到了 圻_荷州博伊西打淼碾
And we get a call from Boise, Idaho.
有一恐怖分子
There's a terrorist who's got,
劫持了整影院
like, the whole movie theater held hostage.
- 然后... - 火^ 好勰 合影可以
- And-- - A-Train? I love you. Can I get a selfie?
然可以啦
Yeah, of course.
等一下
Hang on.
我逾越了落基山} 消缌丝植婪肿 拆除了炸
I ran across the Rockies, took out the terrorist, disarmed the bomb.
- 然后呢  - 用 伙
- Then what? - What you mean, man?
我I了些爆米花 看了《h太平洋:雷霆再起》
Then I got some popcorn, I watched the rest of Pacific Rim: Uprising.
你槭裁床桓嬖V他真相呢
Why don't you tell them the truth?
壬
Nathan.
你...冷oc 好
Just... just be chill, all right?
你背著我偷偷我鹤映鲩T 居然我冷o一下
You're sneaking around with my boys, behind my back, but I need to chill?
- 怎么回事  - 我不知道
- What's going on? - I don't know.
e以槲也土P你
And don't think y'all ain't in some deep shit.
Σ黄 爸爸
Sorry, Dad.
拜托 爸爸 雷吉叔叔 o我v述了他的救援事E
Come on, Dad. Uncle Reggie was just telling us about his saves.
你想告V他 是由我碚f
You want to tell them or should I?
拜托 伙 我e小}大做...
Come on, man, let's not make a big thing--
圻_荷州的那影院 是布朗克斯^的一z影棚
That movie theater in Idaho, that was a soundstage in the Bronx.
那恐怖分子呢
That terrorist, that was a stuntman.
是一特技演T
Those mountains,
那些山是他布的景
they added those in post.
我知道 因楫r我在
I know because I was there.
真的
Is that true?
@事很碗s 知道吧
It's complicated, you know?
不 很 你矶]M行^真正的援救
No, it's simple. Your saves were never real.
你]有真正救^l
You never actually saved anyone.
然而你s大言不M地 ψ约旱募胰巳鲋e
Yet here you are, lying to your own flesh and blood.
我告V^你了
I told you.
你的叔叔不是英雄
Your uncle is no hero.
我不想你靠近他
And I don't want you anywhere near him.
走吧
Come on.
壬
Nathan...
壬 Σ黄
Nathan, I'm sorry.
嘿 等等 o他一crg
Hey, hey. Wait, wait, wait. Give him a second.
你的l我意R到我全家人
Your videos got me to see that my entire family
都被星光@拥偻者洗X了
had been brainwashed by clovergenders like Starlight.
我告V他 他自己做了研究之后 我才能再跟他f
I told them that I couldn't speak to them again until they did their own research.
到F在已三年了
It's been three years now.
你真棒 ^m鸲钒
Good for you. You keep up the fight.
- 可以跟你合影  - 然啦
- Can I get a selfie? - Of course.
- xx - xx
Thank you.
真相
Truth bomb.
可靠公民M的h改橥砩狭c
The Sovereign Citizens meeting has moved to 6:00 p.m.
你真的相信@些事
Do you actually believe all of this?
是f它只是 建立在人恩怨之上的胡言yZ
Or is it just bullshit smeared on top of a personal vendetta?
你嘴巴怎么@么不干
Ain't you a little mouthy one.
欣p你字里行g的N族主x
Appreciate the subtextual racism there,
但我是超人 智者姐妹
but I'm a Supe. Sister Sage.
- 我和祖人一起工作 - 胡f
- I work with Homelander. - Bullshit.
- 天哪 他砹  - 然]有
- Is he here? Goddamn. - Of course not.
他不人到自己和@群 MX子狗屎的混球待在一起
He wouldn't be caught dead with these ringworm-infested cousin fuckers.
不^ 你有C到他
Though there's a chance you could meet him.
首先 我想看看你的超能力
First, I want to see your powers, though.
真是乏味至O啊
Wow, that is... lackluster.
不^我也很大
I'm... strong too, though.
著 重要的是 你在推V什么
Look, what's important is: what are you selling?
我磉@里是榱 分享真相 只f真相...
I'm here to share the truth and nothing but.
你在推V什么
What are you selling?
我口吃了
Did I stutter?
意x
Purpose.
我推V的是意x
I sell purpose.
@些人一o所有
These people got nothing.
也S他因W施康定 而失去了工作 房子或孩子
Maybe they lost a job or a house or a kid to Oxy.
政客并不在乎
Politicians don't give a shit,
主流媒w告V他 要樽约旱哪w色感到羞u
mainstream media tells them to be ashamed of their skin color,
所以呢 我把他聚集在一起 o他v一故事 x予他意x
so, well, I bring 'em together, tell them a story, give them a purpose.
你更愿意相信哪
Which would you rather believe?
自己儆谝 c地下邪鹤鞫的鹗Fw
That you belong to a community of warriors battling a secret evil,
是自己是一孤 o足p重的人
or that you're a lonely, inconsequential nobody
]有人得的人
that no one will ever remember?
深海{洋房g 晚上九c
Deep's Blue Sea Room. 9:00 p.m.
智者]有超能力 Π
Sage has got no powers, right?
她只是X子明
Besides her brains? Nope.
那她偷偷摸摸的是在搞什么
So, why all the sneaking around shite?
抓住她 λM行 威逼她提供信息
Let's just grab her, work her over and rumble what we need.
嘿
Hey.
F在只是在O 好
This is surveillance only, okay?
那好 你坐著 看我做你的工作
All right, you sit tight and watch me do your job.
好了 蛄
All right, enough.
放_我
Get your fuckin' hands off me.
- 回家吧 好  - 不然怎
- Just go home, all right? - Or what?
我在吵架 那就邮职 你看
We have a Barney? Well, come on, then. Have a go.
布 拜托了
Butcher, for fuck's sake.
恼业绞勘男孩_始 你就一直忿忿不平的
You've been gagging for it. Ever since Soldier Boy.
活的火桶 就差屁眼里L出一截Щ鹚髁
Ten pounds of C4 with an inch fuse pokin' out your arse, you are.
那就邮职 看啊 小子
Well, come on, then. Have at it, son.
你不挨打就感X不到后悔
'Cause that's the only way you feel any regret is to get it beaten into you.
你@L太不靠V了 ]e
You're a shit skipper, you are.
休伊完蛋了 喜美子受了重
Hughie's fucked off, Kimiko's hammered.
我在@里已好小r了 他的毫o行
We've been here for hours and still know fuck all.
你害死@群人的
You're gonna get this bloody lot killed.
你吃不下 睡不著
You can't eat, you can't sleep,
s不愿意采取一切行 砉芾磉@群混球
and you ain't willing to do what it takes to run this mob
因槟愫o量 小子
'cause you ain't got the bollocks, son.
想得美 布
Nice try, Butcher.
但你@些]用
But it ain't gonna work.
是啊 你老婆不也f你]用
Yeah, ain't that what your wife said?
你M嘴屁
All that bullshit you pulled,
是我收拾你的子
and the mess you always leave behind
可我每次都回 知道槭裁
for me to clean up, you know why I kept coming back?
因槲蚁搿耙苍S@次有c不同”
'Cause I thought maybe this time, it'll be a little different.
我一起v了那么多困y 伙
All the fucking shit we've been through together, man.
我想也S@一次 也S我和你可以
I thought maybe this time, maybe you and I could just...
再次成樗的兄弟
just be fucking brothers again.
回家吧 伙
Just go home, man.
q太人危U
我知道不要相信U勃辛格 辛格只是臆想
士兵男孩被中央情缶址了
和自由斗士 我要求立即放所有和
嘿
Hey! Hey!
如果你真P心孩子
If you really cared about children...
那就去追捕真正的人子
you'd go after real traffickers...
相信@些鬼管屁用
instead of these fairy tales!
不要
Non!
如果你一定要造成痛苦 就_我戆 @e人就不受苦了
If you must inflict pain, perhaps I can endure so others don't suffer.
嘿
Hey!
快走
Come on.
奶D到@里怎么花了@么久
Took y'all long enough to get here from Trenton.
路上堵了吧
Traffic, am I right?
你他的有何F干
The fuck are you doing here?
眼睛 眼睛是透露一切
The eyes? It's always the eyes.
o
Here.
@是什么
What is this?
那星光支持者的 安全z像^像
Security cam footage of your two Starlighters.
死亡l生r 他距尸ws1.6公里
About a mile from the bodies at time of death.
在20街^之外犯下\⒆锖茈y
It's hard to commit a murder when you're 20 blocks away.
你槭裁匆把@o我
Why are you giving this to us?
你本可以在我家人面前 要我y堪 但你]有
You could have got in my face in front of my family, but you didn't.
- 喈我表_x意吧 - x休伊好了
- Let's call it a thank-you. - Thank Hughie.
我本想把你打得屁L尿流 因槟阕镉得
I would've blasted the shit out of you, and you would've deserved it.
是的 我同意
Yeah, I agree.
沃特y行
嘿
Hey.
退后
Back up.
Back off.
玄色 怎么回...我到底怎么k
Noir, what the fuc-- What the heck are we supposed to do?
- 放_她 - e趼 孩子
- Let her go. - Out of my way, kid.
- 你]事的 - 你保C
- You're gonna be okay. - Do you promise?
我保C
I promise.
你是l
Who are you?
- 我叫... - R恩
- My name is-- - Ryan.
- 是祖人 - 爸爸
It's Homelander! - Dad?
]P系 鹤 有我呢
It's okay, son. I'm here.
我要一起拯救美
We're going to save America together.
邮
Go.
F在把他出去 出去
Throw him hard. Throw him. Now.
天哪
Holy shit.
]事 各位 ]事
It's okay, everyone.
一切都在掌控之中
It's okay. Everything's under control.
你救了我
You saved me.
好姑娘
Good girl.
微笑
Smile.
好的
All right.
我以槲今天不⑷
I thought we weren't killing the guy today.
扮演@角色的指示一c都不明_
I just feel like I'm not getting clear direction for this role.
沃特花@套房庭院快捷酒店
深海{洋
梅芙女王全性e宴d
她f晚上九c 在深海{洋房g 不是
She said 9:00 p.m. in the Deep Blue Sea Room, no?
我_f了
I sure did.
把扔了
Toss your guns.
你的步又花哨又粗俗
Eh, your rifles are garish and vulgar.
他是美人 你@死的蛋
They're American, you fuckin' surrender monkey.
R文 你真的J樽约耗芨我 s不被我lF
Marvin, did you really think you could tail me without me knowing?
所以F在怎幽
So, what now?
@些混蛋是中央情缶值 深度伏的家g
These assholes are CIA. Genuine deep state moles.
他干掉的超英雄比任何人都多
They've taken out more superheroes than anyone in the world.
如果你⒘怂 祖人喜g的
And Homelander would like it if you killed them.
把@看作你的最后一次R吧
Consider it your final audition.
什么R
Audition for what?
他越早死掉 你就越早lF
The sooner they're dead, the sooner you'll find out.
你]有我f的那么了不起
You're not as impressive as I heard.
我要把你打回中去 v人
Oh, I'm gonna send your ass back to China, bitch.
她是日本人
She's Japanese.
你在干什么'
What are you doing?
t眼病 y搞^^了吧
Oh, pink eye. Too much salad tossing, huh?
不 是^敏
No. No, no, no. It's allergies. It's allergies.
- 他的]嘴 - 邮
- Shut the fuck up. - Now!
真他的
Oh, hell nah.
? Hava nagila, hava nagila ?
雷切小姐
? Hava nagila venismecha ?
了不起的雷切小姐
? Hava nagila, hava nagila ?
? Hava nagila venismecha ?
? Hava nera'nena ?
? Hava nera'nena venismecha ?
? Hava nera'nena, hava nera'nena ?
? Hava nera'nena venismecha...
? Uru achim ?
? Hava nera'nena, hava nera'nena ?
? Hava nera'nena...
- 我]子了 - 我也是
- Damn. I'm out. - Me too.
他也是
So are they.
雷切小姐的照相亭
雷切小姐 恭喜
不
No!
x我hc t眼病
Get away from me, pink eye!
不
No!
重大消息
The storm has arrived.
我和斯普林特在B透M q太主x\集F之后
Splinter and I are being attacked by CIA agents
遭到中央情缶痔毓さ墓
after infiltrating a Zionist cabal.
C在哪里
The proof...
C就在@里
the proof is right here.
我召所有人...
Now I'm calling on all--
鞭炮 不
Firecracker! No!
我打你女友 你so能榱
You gonna let me smack your girl like that?
y怪她只拿你朋友 伙
No wonder she put you in the friend zone, mate.
M в⑿劭诵请x_@里
M! Get the boys out of here!
他的
Fuck.
不
No.
不 普R姆一死 我就完了
No, no, no! Not Prime! No!
我圻^你
We loved you.
哪惆l布第一 屠q太人是_局的l_始
From your first Holocaust hoax video.
知道嘛 你...
You know, you--
沃特
l想喝杯奶香十足的美味奶昔
Who wants a creamy, delicious milkshake?
R恩
Oh, Ryan...
戆
Okay, come on.
好啦
Come on.
]P系的
It's okay.
不用心
Don't worry.
好 不用心
Okay? Don't worry.
我保C你@得大量 孤救援的C
You'll get plenty of solo saves, I promise.
但我_J槲业 有助于提高大δ愕年P注度
But I really do think that my being there is good for your numbers.
什么
What?
是的
Yeah.
- 不 我... - 是的
- No. No, no...  - Yes. Yes.
我⒘丝埔
I killed Koy.
你y^就是榱诉@
That's what you're upset about?
榭埔粮械诫y^
Koy?
好吧
Okay.
有事故l生 好
Accidents happen all the time, okay?
人是脆弱的 你o法拯救所有人
Humans are fragile. You can't save them all.
但@不是我的工作
But isn't that our job?
著 科伊樾鄣氖II了身
Look, Koy died doing what he loved.
好
Okay?
- 下次更好的 - 不
- It'll be better next time. - No.
- 的 - 不 我再也不救援了
- Yes. - No, I'm never doing that again.
天哪 我要告V你多少次
Jesus Chr-- How many times do I have to tell you?
他只是人 R恩
They're only human, Ryan.
玩具而已
Toys.
你不能因槟承┦虑槌隽} 就渥约
You can't go around feeling bad about what you are 'cause a few things break.
l在乎呢
Who cares?
你注定比他大
You are destined for so much more.
明白
You understand?
你是天x之人 年p人
You're chosen, young man.
t早你都必接受@一c
Sooner or later, you got to accept it.
相信星光 星光支持女性
o罪
Not guilty! Not guilty! Not guilty!
你_定
Are you sure about this?
我火^@拥幕斓巴ι矶出 s把自己藏在角落
I'm gonna let a shitbag like A-Train step up, but I won't?
你至名w
我能行
I got this.
我勰 星光
We love you, Starlight!
星光
科林黼
你看起碓愀馔疙
You look like shit.
你在哪里
Where are you?
似是而非的否J 小可
Plausible deniability, pumpkin.
@么f吧 我是碜员R森堡的 伯爵夫人 正在永久度假
Let's just say I'm a Contessa from Luxembourg on permanent holiday.
雪 你...
Cherie... you, uh,
你得科林豪瑟
you remember Colin Hauser?
那法官的鹤
The judge's son?
我在戒毒者匿名互助上
I saw him at, uh...
碰了他
Narcotics Anonymous.
他J出你了
Did he recognize you?
我_始交
We started talking.
他^得很Dy 所以我退 在星光之家找到了一份工作 然后...
He was having a hard time, so I helped him get a job at Starlight's House and--
你在跟他上床
You're fucking him, right?
拜托 塞日
For fuck's sake, Serge,
你是怎么回事  怎么老是放不下那些下三E的人
what is it with you and taking in strays all the time?
我不是故意要@N事l生的
I didn't mean for it to happen.
我天天都到他
I was just seeing him day after day,
感情迅速升 然后...
one thing led to another, and--
他lF你\⒘怂家人r怎
So what happens when he finds out you murdered his family?
打印你保C的都比你的保C值X
Your promise isn't worth the piece of paper it's printed on!
我...不...我不明白
I don't understand that.
之前...
Just, earlier--
之前 你f保C照爸爸
Earlier, you said that you-- you said that
但你根本都]照他
you promised to handle Dad, but you're not handling shit!
你能小c
Can you just lower your voice?
不到你ξ抑甘之_
No, no, no. You don't get to tell me what to do,
- 好  - 好
- okay? - Okay.
你x_的那天是星期五
The day you left, it was a Friday.
你送我去W校
You walked me to school,
保Co我I比利的演出票
and you promised to buy us tickets to Billy Joel.
我激拥身l抖
I was vibrating with excitement.
那是我最后一次到你
That was the last I ever saw you.
之后的一星期 我都站在前T那里
I spent a week standing by the front door,
告V爸爸你回 你怎么不回砟 你保C^啊
telling Dad you'd be back, because why wouldn't you be? You promised.
但你的保C]有任何意x
But your promise didn't mean anything.
我非常抱歉 休伊
I'm so, so sorry, Hughie.
@事c你我oP
This isn't about you and me.
PI是什么δ愀赣H碚f才是最好的
This is about what's best for your dad.
你不知道什么λ最好 什么ξ最好
You don't know what's best for him. You don't know what's best for either of us.
默F在_始 ]有我在 你就不能和t生
From now on, you don't talk to a doctor without me,
]有我字 你就不能做出任何tQ定
you don't make any medical decisions without me signing off.
如果你Υ瞬M
And if you don't like it,
我就把你告上法庭
I'll take you to court.
求法院Zo你的授
I'll challenge you for power of attorney.
把你那些迷迭香精油垃圾扔掉
And get rid of all your fucking rosemary oil crap.
爸爸它 起硐袷阂
Dad would hate it and it smells like shit.
卡特琳_德里克博士 R床治
~s市W亮恐怖M
xx
Thanks.
你之前那幼 你...
What you did back there, you...
你救了我
...you saved our asses.
你不救我
You should've left me.
做一名秀的L
To be a good skipper,
一定得混蛋
you gotta be a right asshole.
]有z的余地
Ain't no room for compassion.
正_的做法是抓住智者那v人
The right move to make was to nab that cunt Sage.
相反 你s把英雄克星нM了陷阱
Instead, you walked the boys into a trap,
然后冒著生命危U去拯救某
and then risked their lives to save some twat
⒃诹月人廊サ谋康
who's gonna be dead in six months.
我@次很幸\ 但下次...
We was lucky, but next time,
有人死
someone's gonna die.
回自己的一生
I look back at my life,
我所看到的一切
and all I see
都是我造成的子
are the messes I've made.
我搞砸了
I've fucked it up.
每一步都搞砸了
Every step.
可我]有rg收拾@些子了
And I ain't got time to fix it.
也S
But maybe...
也S我可以利用剩下的rg做一件事
maybe I can do one thing right with the time I got left.
_保R恩安全
Get Ryan safe.
但我自己是做不到的
I can't do that alone.
]有你我做不到
I can't do it without you.
求你了
Please.
太M隘了 布
Too fucking little, Butcher.
太他晚了
Too fucking late.
字幕翻g:P
意O督 肖雪